{
    "id": "0b0c18b3aa9c430ab230b463efd33667",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The state of affairs …………………. sure to cause him anxiety.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are",
                "has",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "An advocate and a doctor ....................... on this street.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "live",
                "lives",
                "are living"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The introduction of radical reforms ...................... opposed by the aristocracy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were",
                "has",
                "had"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Slow and steady ………………….. the race.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "win",
                "wins",
                "is winning",
                "has won"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He …………………. hardly sat down when someone knocked at the door.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "had",
                "was"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She has been working here ……………….. six years now.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "from",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I saw him six months ..................... .",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "before",
                "ago",
                "past"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Were you foolish ……………….. to trust him?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "also",
                "as well",
                "enough"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "I wish you …………………. stop complaining like this.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "should",
                "would",
                "will"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "………………….. you obey my instructions, you will be killed.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Unless",
                "If",
                "Whether"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}